module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? Prelude',
    a: 'Fiat',
    b: 'Honda',
    c: 'Suzuki',
    d: 'Acura',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? Commodore',
    a: 'Oldsmobile',
    b: 'Lexus',
    c: 'Volkwagen',
    d: 'Holden',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? Edge',
    a: 'Chrysler',
    b: 'Ford',
    c: 'Hyndai',
    d: 'Suzuki',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? M1',
    a: 'Porsche',
    b: 'Fiat',
    c: 'BMW',
    d: 'Ford',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? X1/9',
    a: 'Range Rover',
    b: 'Suzuki',
    c: 'Fiat',
    d: 'BMW',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? Jimny',
    a: 'Honda',
    b: 'Hyndai',
    c: 'Suzuki',
    d: 'Oldsmobile',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? Sierra',
    a: 'Ford',
    b: 'Buick',
    c: 'Chrysler',
    d: 'Dodge',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? 944',
    a: 'Mercury',
    b: 'Porsche',
    c: 'Daewoo',
    d: 'BMW',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? RX',
    a: 'Ford',
    b: 'Mercury',
    c: 'Lexus',
    d: 'BMW',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which car manufacturer produced this model? Town and Country',
    a: 'Buick',
    b: 'Chrysler',
    c: 'Oldsmobile',
    d: 'Pontiac',
    answer: 'b'
  }
];
